Real Cap
My dad brought this RC plane from America.
Nothing can match its speed.
Amesome! Let me fly the plane after you do.
I wanna fly it, too!
Not you, Nobita!
But why?
'Cause you don't know how to fly a plane and you will surely crash it.
Right, if you want to fly a plane, buy it yourself.
Left
Right
What's up, Nobita-kun?
I'm flying a fantastic RC plane.
Why don't you get a real one?
My mom won't buy me and I wanted one now!
Suneo's parents buy him everything he wants, I envy him!
Down, my boy
That was sentimental
In that case, I've got just the right thing for you.
A RC plane?
You're too naive.
Real Cap!
This has nothing to do with a RC plane!
Wear it and then you have to imagine whatever you want...
...and then it appears right in front of you.
A real RC plane?!
No, it's just the illusion and you'll be the only one who can see it.
Well damn that's boring.
Give it a try, I bet nothing's more fun having a RC plane
Time to rack your brains, Nobita. The plane will soon appear in front of you
It's gotta be better than Suneo's.
Well, did you like it?
Amazing!
Not as good
Well that's still your imagination Nobita
This catalogue might be of use. Here you go
Here I go
Think hard
Wow, this is awesome...
I can even feel the nozzle of the plane... the smell of the gasoline too, it's all too real!
You can remove the cap now, you can still see the RC plane
Thanks for that! Wait, I'm gonna treat you to tons of Dorayaki... Hang on
Isn't this nice? A lifetime of Dorayaki
Well, I can't see anything... Only you imagined it
Yeah right, I can see it
Delicious! Nothing beats this
It's pity that you can't eat this, Doraemon
I can't resist myself eating the delicious Dorayaki! Gimme the cap~
Very delicious
Giant, Please return it to me now
Bug off! I'm flyin' dis plane now and so be it! Aw dis is so fun
There they are. I can easily defeat Suneo's plane. Here we go
Speed up
Go round
Attaboy, that's the way she flies
Yeah! I've done this! Hurray
Oi, whassup mate
Ah well he's always in his own stupid world. I don't give a damn you know
Yeah I know right
Alright time for something more interesting
Be ready!
Never dare to tease me again!
Oi, wut's he doing now
He's gone crazy I guess. I gotta go
This cap is so awesome
Shizu-chan, I've got something cool
Aw, isn't this cute?
I'm always right
That's right Nobi-san
Isn't that awesome
Yep, cute teddy bear. Thank you
Shizu-chan, why are you holding  your hands like that?
Aww, what a cute panda. I used Nobita's cap
Cute panda?
Nay, I cunt see anyding
I can see this cute panda
Yeah just put on that cap Nobita's having, and all you have to do is think hard to get the stuff you want
You sure? That cap?
Oui nobita give me dat cap now
I'm not sure if he'd return it
Give me now
I want a lion
Attack!
Attack?
This is what you get when you don't obey me
Damn, I should have known that it has no effect on others
Alright all i gutta do now is to think of all the stuff I need. That one...
Wow there dey come
Nicey-nicey!
Wow!
I can't see anything...
I'm wrapping all of these and carrying them on my cycle home
I'm done with this! Give it to me now!
No way! I've just borrowed it for a shurt time
Meet ya later guyz
WHAT
Giant never returned back the Real Cap after he used it?!
Yeah do something
Yeah dont worry, I'm bringing it back
Really?
Yeah, he never returns borrowed stuff. Time to teach him a lesson
He's sleeping
Dinosaur Slippers and Megaphone
All ready, Nobita?
I'm a Dinosaur!
Oi, someone help me!
Giant is experiencing it real time.
He's gonna have a hard time once he wakes up!
Let's return now that we've retrieved real cap!
Nay it was a dream
Oi stop chasing me! Leave me alone
Someone help me!
Leave me alune!!
What's wrong with Giant?
I wonder what's chasing Giant?
I wonder!
Help!! Leave me alone!